

# Pritam Dhande

Career Objective

Passionate Front-End Web Developer with 1.5+ years experience building and maintaining responsive websites in the technology and service industry. Highly skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React Js alongside modern frameworks and libraries. Interested about accessibility and usability of modern websites.

pritamdhande11@gmail.com

Nagpur, India

in in.linkedin.com/in/pritam-dhande-17374b1a0

+91 7758036768

👿 wardhatourism.in

github.com/Pritam-Dhande

#### **EDUCATION**

MCA (Master of Computer Application) Nagpur University

2022 - 2024

**B.Sc.** (Computer Science)

**Nagpur University** 

2018 - 2021 60.59%

Web Development Internship

Full Stack Web Development Internship at Edureka in (MERN Stack).

01/2022 - 07/2022 **CURRICULUM** 

work.

Virtual

- Experience with web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Proficient in Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express JS, React JS, and Node JS for language and framework
- Design and code new features and enhancements.
- Skilled in version control systems, specifically GitHub using GitBash.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### (UI/UX DEVELOPER)

1 year of UI/UX development experience at Probuz Technologies Pvt Ltd, Nagpur. Transitioned from a two-month trainee role to a Developer within the same company.

02/2022 - 01/2023 Onside

Roles and Responsibilities

- Handling UI Part of different types of websites.
- Working as a Mentor for newly joined intern.

### React JS Development Internship Sprime Tech IT Solution, Nagpur

08/2023 - 11/2023 Onside

#### React JS Developer

Sprime Tech IT Solution, Nagpur

01/2024 - Present Onside

Roles and Responsibilities

• React JS developer using Visual Studio 2022, working on daily tasks in React JS development, leveraging Asp.net MVC Core Framework for project building.

#### **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL & COMPANY PROJECTS

Phonese Mobile App & Website (Company Project)

 Making an User Interface of Phonese Mobile app https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.phonese.phonese & Website https://phonese.biz/ Using front end technologies.

React JS E-commerce Website (Personal Project)

Currently working on making E-commerce website https://pritamecommerce.netlify.app/ using react js library.

#### **COURSES & CERTIFICATES**

Front End Web Development Bootcamp From DevTown (2023)

TCS iON Career Edge - Young Professional Course From TCS iON (2022)

National Level Java Programming Quiz from Hislop College Nagpur (2020)

The Fundamental Of Digital Marketing course From Google Digital Unlocked (2019)

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

#### INTERESTS

**Exploring Internet** Web Development Photography Video Editing Researching